<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
	<maintainer type="person">
		<email>composizion3@protonmail.ch</email>
		<name>Michele Renosto walkingcorpse</name>
	</maintainer>
	<longdescription>Chromium with the option to do an Official build and more configuration options</longdescription>
	<use>
		<flag name="component-build">Split build into more shared libraries to speed up linking. Mostly intended for debugging and development, NOT RECOMMENDED for general use.</flag>
		<flag name="hangouts">Enable support for Google Hangouts features such as screen sharing</flag>
		<flag name="jumbo-build">Combine source files to speed up build process.</flag>
		<flag name="pic">Disable optimized assembly code that is not PIC friendly</flag>
		<flag name="proprietary-codecs">Enable proprietary codecs like H.264, MP3</flag>
		<flag name="suid">Build the SUID sandbox, which is only needed on CONFIG_USER_NS=n kernels</flag>
		<flag name="system-icu">Use system icu instead of the bundled one</flag>
		<flag name="tcmalloc">Use bundled tcmalloc instead of system malloc</flag>
		<flag name="widevine">Unsupported closed-source DRM capability (required by Netflix VOD)</flag>
		<flag name="official">Optimize it like an official build, on Linux this turns on LTO and produces a faster binary</flag>
		<flag name="extensions">Enable extensions</flag>
		<flag name="debug">Make a debug build</flag>
		<flag name="oculus">Build with Oculus support</flag>
		<flag name="profiling">Compile in such a way as to enable profiling of the generated code. For example, don't omit the frame pointer and leave in symbols. </flag>
		<flag name="vr">Enable VR support</flag>
		<flag name="vulkan">Enable experimental vulkan backend</flag>
		<flag name="wayland">Indicates if Wayland display server support is enabled</flag>
		<flag name="fieldtrial-testing-like-official">Set to true make a build that disables activation of field trial tests specified in testing/variations/fieldtrial_testing_config_*.json </flag>
		<flag name="vr-data">Whether to include VR extras like test APKs in non-VR-specific targets</flag>
		<flag name="asan">Compile for Address Sanitizer to find memory bugs</flag>
		<flag name="unsafedevfeatures">Has developer-friendly features that may weaken or disable security measures like sandboxing or ASLR. </flag>
		<flag name="gtk3">Whether to compile against GTKv3 instead of GTKv2</flag>
		<flag name="vaapi">Indicates if VA-API-based hardware acceleration is to be used</flag>
		<flag name="gcc">Compile with GCC, this is unsupported upstream and requires GCC 8</flag>
		<flag name="cfi">Compile with Control Flow Integrity to protect virtual calls and casts.</flag>
		<flag name="debug-devtools">If debug_devtools is set to true, JavaScript files for DevTools are stored as is and loaded from disk. Otherwise, a concatenated file is stored in resources.pak. It is still possible to load JS files from disk by passing --debug-devtools cmdline switch. </flag>
		<flag name="strip-debug-symb">Strip debug symbols</flag>
		<flag name="lld">Use the faster LLD linker with Clang</flag>
		<flag name="swiftshader">Enable an is a high-performance CPU-based implementation of the OpenGL ES and Direct3D 9 graphics APIs, useful for bad old integrated graphic cards.</flag>
	</use>
</pkgmetadata>
